what-when-how.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Statement

Thank you for visiting what-when-how.com provided by The-Crankshaft Publishing. Our privacy policy is clear: We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.

Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website:

Information Collected and Stored Automatically

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

1\. The Internet domain (for example, “xcompany.com” if you use a private Internet access account, or “yourschool.edu” if you connect from a university’s domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;  
2\. The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;  
3\. The date and time you access our site;  
4\. The pages you visit; and  
5\. If you linked to The-Crankshaft Publishing’s what-when-how.com from another website, the address of that website.

We use this information to help us make the site more useful to visitors — to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.

If You Send Us Personal Information

If you choose to provide us with personal information — by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through the website — we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. The information you provide will only be used for what-when-how.com marketing purposes and will not be sold to ANY external organizations.

Site Security

1\. For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs commercial software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.  
2\. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, no other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. Raw data logs are used for no other purposes and are scheduled for regular destruction in accordance with National Archives and Records Administration guidelines.  
3\. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

Prohibitions

The-Crankshaft Publishing’s what-when-how.com will not link to any website that exhibits hate, bias, or discrimination. Furthermore, The-Crankshaft Publishing reserves the right to deny or remove any link that contains misleading information or unsubstantiated claims, or is determined to be in conflict with The-Crankshaft Publishing mission or policies.

Advertising

what-when-how.com displays advertisements.On its several pages,as a result of which we use doubledart cookie to track user preference and interest categories.  
After collecting information about users interest,advertisements more specific to his or her location and interest are displayed.  
To achieve this doubledart cookie is stored in your browser files.  
You can opt out from double-dart cookie,by instaling doubledart opt out cookie in your browser,from doubleclick website:

http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/opting_out.aspx

No personal information is stored by doubledart cookie about the users who visit what-when-how.com

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.what-when-how.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.what-when-how.com does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.what-when-how.com  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.what-when-how.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.what-when-how.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.what-when-how.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.what-when-how.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
